GENE LEE

I am a junior web developer with 3+ years of experience developing user interfaces, debugging code, testing, and managing websites. I am a quick learner, and am looking forward to learning new programs and skills throughout my career.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Software Engineer II 09/2019 – present Dulles Glass & Mirror, Manassas, VA, United States

- Used Azure Devops to deploy new iterations of software
- Developed and maintained multiple ecommerce websites in both the frontend and backend using ASP .NET MVC Framework and .NET core
- Updated database and managed inventory
- Implement new features into the websites and fixed bugs
- Managed the company's Amazon seller central account

Entry Level Software 05/2018 - 09/2019 **Engineer**

Dulles Glass & Mirror, Manassas, VA, United States

- Developed and maintained multiple ecommerce websites in both the frontend and backend using ASP .NET MVC Framework and .NET core
- Updated database and managed inventory
- Implemented key new features into the websites and fixed bugs
- Updated websites to a new mobile responsive design
- Managed the company's Amazon seller central account

Software and Test 12/2016 - 05/2018 **Engineer Intern**

Dulles Glass & Mirror, Fairfax, VA, United States

 Implemented front-end code (web design) for multiple ecommerce websites/applications as a

web developer.

- Worked with the ASP.NET framework, C#, and Amazon Web Services (DynamoDB, S3).
 Tested software for web applications.
- Experience working and cooperating with a team, managing inventory, and developing in both front and back end.

WORK FXPFRIFNCE

Worked closely with senior developer and trained under him

Programmer & Level 08/2017 - 05/2018 **Designer**

Computer Game Design Senior Capstone, Fairfax, VA, United States

- Worked on a unique game experience in a team of 3, for a year-long project.
- Managed and developed the game concept and mechanics from start to finish.
- Developed on the Unity 3Dgame engine with C#, using models made in 3DS Max and Autodesk Maya.

EDUCATION

B.S. Economics 09/2013 – 05/2018 George Mason University, Fairfax, VA, United States

Minors in Information Technology and Computer Game Design

AUGUST 2013 - MAY 2018

• GPA: 3.27

SKILLS

Programming languages

Java, Javascript, C#, Python, SOL

Web Technologies

Rest, HTML5, CSS, Bootstrap, jQuery, JSON, ASP .NET MVC, .NET Core, Azure Devops

Data Management

MySQL, DynamoDB, Microsoft Server Management Studio

KEYWORDS



SOCIAL MEDIA





LinkedIn

Portfolio